nobuna.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy - Nobuna

## Summary

In this Nobuna.com GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy you can  
find out:

  1. About Us
  2. The Collection of Data (Including Personal Data) & GDPR
  3. What Types of Data Do We Collect & When?
  4. Is My Personal Data & Other Information Safe & Secure?
  5. How can I Access, Amend, Correct and/or Delete my Personal Data?
  6. International Data Transfers
  7. Disclosure of Personal Data
  8. How Long Do We Keep Your Information
  9. Our Cookies Policy
  10. Changes to this Nobuna.com GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy  
Policy, & Cookies Policy

## About Us

Europymes Servicios Integrales S.L, the company which operates  
Nobuna.com, provides WooCommerce and WordPress Premium Plugins &  
Themes at discounted prices and website monitoring services to its  
customers alerting them when their website has gone done or is  
experiencing performance issues. Nobuna.com also provides other features  
that advise its customers on, amongst other things, domain expiration, SSL  
certificate expiration and validity, the presence of vulnerabilities on  
their website.

Europymes Servicios Integrales has been launched in May 2012 and is a  
company incorporated in Spain with company number B83247627.  Our  
office is at Urano 9 Bajo A – 28925 (Alcorcon) Madrid, Spain.

## The Collection of Data (Including Personal Data) & GDPR

The EU General Data Protection Regulation EU 2016/679 (“GDPR”) comes into  
effect on 25thMay 2018 and will replace all the European Data Protection  
Laws. The GDPR strengthens and unifies data protection rights for  
individuals throughout the EU.

The GDPR is intended to give you more control over how companies such as  
Nobuna.com collect data from you and how it is used.  In particular  
GDPR focuses on data collected which is “Personal Data”; such personal  
data may be your email address, your first and last name, or your IP  
address.  Where we collect Personal Data this policy tells you where  
is it collected, the type of data that is collected, the legal basis upon  
which we process that data, the reason for collecting the data, and the  
use we make of the data.  Notes are also provided which provide more  
information on the processing of that particular data source.

## What Types of Data do we Collect & When?

Below sets out the data that Nobuna.com gathers from our website visitors  
and our users.  We detail below when we collect data, the type of  
data we collect and then what we do with that data and why.

### Signing-up for a Nobuna.com account

Point of Collection: |  

Signing-up for a Nobuna.com account  
  
---|---  
Type of Personal Data Collected: | Upon sign-up we collect: 

  * email address;

  * password; and/or

  * IP address

Basis for Processing:  | The basis upon which we process your personal data is as follows: 

  * when you sign-up for a Nobuna.com account you are giving us  
your clear consent that we may process your personal data for  
those specific purposes set-out in our Terms & Conditions  
and this Privacy Policy; and/or

  * the processing of your personal data is necessary for the  
contract you have entered into with us, and enables us to  
deliver Nobuna.com service to you.

Reason for Collection:  | The data collected enables us to create your account and give you  
a unique and secure way of logging into your account  
Use of Data Collected: | We will use this data to: 

  * enable you to login securely to your account

  * send you emails relating to your account and the Nobuna.com  
service including by way of example, on-boarding emails,  
product updates, and

Notes: | 

  * This data is not shared with any third parties.

  * If you do not wish to receive these emails please contact us.

  * Nobuna.com account passwords are encrypted using Bcrypt; we  
do not store raw passwords.

  * This data is processed and stored within France.

### Creation of a Paid Account

Point of Collection: |  

Creation of a Paid Account  
  
---|---  
Type of Personal Data Collected: | When you upgrade to a paid account may collect some or all of the  
following (“Paid Account Details”): 

  * your first and last name;

  * an additional email address for your billing contact;

  * the name of your company;

  * the address of your company; and

  * your company VAT number.

In addition the following information (“Payment Details”) are  
collected via our payment gateway:

  * your long debit or credit card number;

  * the card expiry date; and

  * CVC details.

Basis for Processing:  | The basis upon which we process your personal data is as follows: 

  * when you sign-up for a Nobuna.com account you are giving us  
your clear consent that we may process your personal data for  
those specific purposes set-out in our Terms & Conditions  
and this Nobuna.com GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy  
Policy; and/or

  * the processing of your personal data is necessary for the  
contract you have entered into with us, and enables us to  
deliver the Nobuna.com service to you.

Reason for Collection: | The data collected enables you to subscribe to a Nobuna.com Paid  
Account.  
Use of Data Collected: | We will use this data to manage all aspects of your Nobuna.com  
Paid Account subscription including by way of example: 

  * creation of a Nobuna.com subscription;

  * dealing with any queries relating to your subscription and  
billing;

  * dealing with payment queries; and

  * managing sales leads and renewals.

Notes: | 

  * We make use of a customer-relationship-management tool called  
SalesFlare to help us manage our sales leads.  The  
information we share may include your name and/or email  
address.

  * We do not share your Paid Account Details with any third  
parties.

  * Your Payment Details are collected, encrypted and securely  
stored by: (a) when using “PayPal”, by PayPal (Europe) S.à  
r.l. et Cie, S.C.A; or (b) when making a payment by debit or  
credit cards provided by Visa Europe Ltd, MasterCard Europe  
S.A., Discover, American Express or other applicable card  
networks, by Stripe Inc. on our website by our payment gateway  
provider Stripe.

  * We do not hold any of your Payment Details.

  * Paid Account Details are processed and stored within France.

### Your Navigation & Use of the Nobuna.com Website & Service

Point of Collection: | Your Navigation & Use of the Nobuna.com Website &  
Service  
---|---  
Type of Data Collected: | When you arrive at the Nobuna.com website we may use visitor  
analytics tool to track how you arrived on our website, how you  
navigate through the website and on to sign-up. 

We may also track the use you make of the Nobuna.com service,  
including by way of example, when and how you make use of  
individual features, when and how you set-up tests and/or alerts.

(collectively “Navigational Data”)  
  
Basis for Processing:  | The basis upon which we process your Navigational Data is as  
follows: 

  * when you sign-up for a Nobuna.com account you are giving us  
your clear consent that we may process your personal data for  
those specific purposes set-out in our Terms & Conditions  
and this Nobuna.com GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy  
Policy; and/or

  * the processing of your personal data is necessary for the  
contract you have entered into with us, and enables us to  
deliver the Nobuna.com service to you.

Reason for Collection:  | The Navigational Data collected enables us to understand how you  
and/or our users as a whole make use of the Nobuna.com website and  
service.  
Use of Data Collected: | We may use the Navigational Data collected to: 

  * understand how you and our other users arrive at the  
Nobuna.com website and navigate our website;

  * understand how you use the product;

  * use your data individually and/or aggregated to improve the  
usability of the product; and/or

  * use your data to answer your customer support queries.

Notes: | 

  * When you sign-up for a Nobuna.com account the Navigational  
Data which has been collected via Google Analytics.  Up  
until the point of account creation (at which point processing  
consent is given), we do not tie any of your Navigational Data  
to your Personal Data.

  * We can opt-out of Google Analytics by  
clicking here.  This will not stop you from  
experiencing the full benefits of the Nobuna.com website and  
service.

  * Save as set out above, we do not share your information with  
any third parties.

## Is My Personal Data & Other Information Safe & Secure?

We employ a number of steps-and-measures to ensure that all information  
and Personal Data we collect is protected from unauthorised access, use  
and/or disclosure.

As well as putting in place technological security measures, we also  
ensure that our entire team are trained in data security and that each of  
them have contractual obligations in their contracts of employment not to  
disclose information to anyone who is not entitled to have it.

## How can I Access, Amend, Correct and/or Delete my Personal Data?

You have the right at any time to access any Personal Data we hold about  
you, and where you feel the Personal Information that we hold is not  
correct, to request that the Personal Information is corrected.  You  
also have the right to have your Personal Information deleted.

All of the Personal Information, along with other data collected (as  
noted in the table above) is information that you can access, amend or  
delete by logging into your Nobuna.com Account.

If you have any questions about accessing, correcting, amending, or  
deleting your information then you can contact us.

## International Data Transfers

Any and all Personal Data that we collect from within the EU/ European  
Economic Area (EEA) and Switzerland is processed and stored within the UK.

In the event that Personal Data is transferred outside of the EU/EEA  
and/or Switzerland, we ensure that at all times that we provide the same  
level of privacy protection as is required by the EU-US Privacy Shield  
framework and/or any other framework determined by the European Commission  
to provide adequate protection for data transfers from the EU and/or  
Switzerland to the US.

## Third-Party Service Providers

We share information, including personal information, with our  
third-party service providers that we use to provide hosting for and  
maintenance of our Websites, customer service, application development,  
backup, storage, payment processing, analytics and other services for us.  
These third-party service providers may have access to or process your  
personal information for the purpose of providing these services for us.  
We do not permit our third-party service providers to use the personal  
information that we share with them for their marketing purposes or for  
any other purpose than in connection with the services they provide to us.

## Disclosure of Personal Data

We will not disclose your Personal Data to any third party unless as  
otherwise explicitly set out in this Nobuna.com GDPR Compliance Statement  
& Privacy Policy.  We may however at times be required by law, a  
competent regulatory authority, by a court, to disclose your Personal  
Information.   Where this occurs we will where it is practical  
for us to do so and/or to the extent that we are not otherwise restricted  
from doing so, notify you before disclosing your Personal Data.

## How Long Do We Keep Your Information

The length of time we keep your Personal Data and other information will  
depend on both the nature of the information we have gathered and the use  
we make of that information.

Unless we are required by law to keep your Personal Data and other  
information for a certain amount of time, we will not ordinarily keep your  
information longer than is necessary, given the purpose for what that  
information for collected by us.

## Our Cookies Policy

### What is a Cookie?

A cookie is a small text file, which is unique to you and allows the  
Nobuna.com Websites to recognize your computer or any such other device  
which you may use from time-to-time for browsing the Internet  
(collectively “Your Computer”).

We may use cookies and other “tags” (sometimes referred to as  
“web-beacons” or “pixel-tags”) (collectively “Cookie(s)”) to provide you  
with a more personalised service on the Nobuna.com Websites or to aid or  
track your navigation around our website.

If you do choose not to accept any of our Cookies some of the  
functionality or personalized version of the Nobuna.com Websites may not  
be available to you.

### When Do We Use Cookies?

When you register to receive information on the Nobuna.com Websites  
and/or register to use the Nobuna.com Services we may allocate a Cookie to  
Your Computer (“Registration Cookie”).

A Registration Cookie may hold any information collection during your  
registration or sign-up and allows us to recognize you and provide you  
with the information or services that you require. If your browser is not  
set to accept Cookies you may not be able to register for and/or sign-up  
for the Nobuna.com Services.

In addition to Registration Cookies we may from time-to-time use other  
types of Cookie to gather information. Such Cookies may include, but not  
be limited to “session-based” Cookies which are allotted to Your Computer  
for the duration of your visit to the Nobuna.com Websites, but will be  
deleted when you close down your Internet browser.

All use of Cookie gathered information is made in accordance with our  
Nobuna.com GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy.

## Changes to this Nobuna.com GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy  
Policy, & Cookies Policy

This Nobuna.com GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy, along  
with our Cookies Policy, may be modified from time-to-time.  We  
recommend that you regularly review this page to ensure that you are aware  
of any changes made to it.

You will be bound by any changes to this Nobuna.com GDPR Compliance  
Statement & Privacy Policy from the moment you make any use of the  
Nobuna.com service after amendments have been made.

In the event that we make any material changes to this Nobuna.com GDPR  
Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy we will take reasonable efforts  
to notify you of those changes, by way of example only, whether through  
in-app notification or by email.

## Nobuna.com GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy – Last  
Updated 24 April 2018
